<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Feggah</title>
    <link>https://feggah.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Feggah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:54:16 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://feggah.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Byte or rune: is there any difference?</title>
      <link>https://feggah.com/posts/byte-or-rune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:54:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feggah.com/posts/byte-or-rune/</guid>
      <description>When you are creating algorithms to deal with strings in Go, especially when using for loops, it&amp;rsquo;s common to use either a regular for loop (using each item of the slice as a byte) or a for range loop (using each item as a rune). When choosing which one to use, you could have asked youself &amp;ldquo;Is there any difference?&amp;rdquo;. That&amp;rsquo;s what we are going to talk about in this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are DORA metrics?</title>
      <link>https://feggah.com/posts/what-are-dora-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 10:07:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feggah.com/posts/what-are-dora-metrics/</guid>
      <description>This post has my opinionated ideas about this topic. We don&amp;rsquo;t need to agree, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to use it as a starting point to discuss.
 DORA provides a clear approach to understanding the effectiveness of a software delivery process. One of the keys of DORA is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t attempt to measure productivity, instead, they are focused on measuring velocity and stability.
There are four key metrics divided into two groups that are used to measure the performance of teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://feggah.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 06:18:29 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feggah.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Gabriel Ferreira, I&amp;rsquo;m from Brazil, and I work as a Software Engineer. For most of my career, I developed internal developer platforms to help the company&amp;rsquo;s internal clients (usually developers), primarily seeking to improve their productivity and autonomy. I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about open-source, and I like to stay in touch with the community of projects I&amp;rsquo;m involved with.
Even though I worked with IDPs, I consider myself a Software Engineer instead of an SRE/DevOps Engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
