<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Feggah</title>
    <link>https://feggah.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Feggah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 16:21:10 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://feggah.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick tips: How to change function return value from deferred call</title>
      <link>https://feggah.com/posts/how-to-change-function-return-value-from-deferred-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 16:21:10 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feggah.com/posts/how-to-change-function-return-value-from-deferred-call/</guid>
      <description>It is common to use defer in Golang and there are some cases where you could want to check if the deferred call returned an error or not. In such a case, how could you check and pass the deferred error to the function caller?
The example below shows an example of using defer with Close():
func createFile(name string) error { f, err := os.Create(name) if err != nil { return err } defer f.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PlatformCon 2023 notes</title>
      <link>https://feggah.com/posts/platformcon-2023-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 09:55:24 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feggah.com/posts/platformcon-2023-notes/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents     Introduction Build abstractions, not illusions 🌟 How to measure ROI and make your platform effect visible  Roadmap to ROIs  Proxy metrics Visibility     Build golden paths for day 50, not for day 1! 🌟 Backstage does not an internal platform make! The power of collaboration: Why platform engineers should engage in open source contributions Authorization at scale in platform environments Drift detection in multi-region AWS deployments for enterprises using DriftCTL Shorten the feedback loop: How to optimize developer experience and system design Why is it so hard to create a great Platform-as-a-Product?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Byte or rune: is there any difference?</title>
      <link>https://feggah.com/posts/byte-or-rune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:54:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feggah.com/posts/byte-or-rune/</guid>
      <description>When you are creating algorithms to deal with strings in Go, especially when using for loops, it&amp;rsquo;s common to use either a regular for loop (using each item of the slice as a byte) or a for range loop (using each item as a rune). When choosing which one to use, you could have asked youself &amp;ldquo;Is there any difference?&amp;rdquo;. That&amp;rsquo;s what we are going to talk about in this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are DORA metrics?</title>
      <link>https://feggah.com/posts/what-are-dora-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 10:07:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feggah.com/posts/what-are-dora-metrics/</guid>
      <description>This post has my opinionated ideas about this topic. We don&amp;rsquo;t need to agree, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to use it as a starting point to discuss.
 DORA provides a clear approach to understanding the effectiveness of a software delivery process. One of the keys of DORA is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t attempt to measure productivity, instead, they are focused on measuring velocity and stability.
There are four key metrics divided into two groups that are used to measure the performance of teams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
